coreonline.com 2013-06-30

# SQUARE ENIX

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We, Square Enix Limited, are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. 

This Privacy Policy relates to our website at _eu.square-enix.com_ , the European parts of the website at _www.playonline.com_ and any other websites and online services operated by us (collectively, the “ **Site** ”). 

This Privacy Policy explains how we use any personal information that we collect about you when you use the Site. Further details of how we use your information is set out in our _Cookies Policy_ and in the _Square Enix Online Services Privacy Policy_ , each of which forms part of this Privacy Policy. 

By using the Site, you consent to the collection, storage and use of your personal information as described below. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. 

**Topics:**

_Data protection compliance_

_The information we collect from you_

_An important note to parents or guardians_

_How we use personal information_

_Disclosure of your personal information_

_Tracking technology and IP addresses_

_Cookie technology_

_Where we store your personal information_

_Information security_

_Other websites_

_Opting out_

_Access to your information_

_How to contact us_

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_

**Data protection compliance**

This Site is controlled by us from our offices in the United Kingdom (“ **UK** ”). Personal information collected from the Site is processed in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “ **Act** "), which regulates the processing of personal data in the UK. We are registered as a data controller in accordance with the Act and comply with UK data protection and privacy law. 

If you choose to visit the Site from outside the UK, you do so at your own risk, with the understanding that personal information collected from the Site may be collected, stored and used in a country whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home country. 

**The information we collect from you**

When you use the Site (such as when registering as a member and/or using our paid-for services), we may ask you to provide us with personal information that identifies you personally (including “personal data” and “sensitive personal data”, as defined in the Act). This may include your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, fax number, gender, date of birth, country and/or preferred language. From time to time, you may be asked to submit personal information in order to receive or use services on the Site or for the purposes further described in this Privacy Policy. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable us to provide you with the services you select. If you do not provide us with all or part of the personal information requested, some services on the Site may not be available to you. 

Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

You may decide to make certain information available for other users of our services to see (for example, in the course of playing an online game). In this context, you should only provide information that you are entirely comfortable with providing, and we strongly recommend that you do not provide any details that could be used to make personal contact with you. 

We may also collect certain anonymous usage data, such as pages visited and services used within the Site. This information is not personally identifiable information and generally is not aggregated with your personal information. We generally use usage data to improve our services to you and to customise and enhance your experience of the Site. 

**An important note to parents or guardians**

We encourage parents or guardians to take an active interest in their children's use of the internet and the Site. Parents or guardians should be aware that there are software tools available online that screens objectionable content and allows you to prevent children from disclosing their personal information without your permission. 

We will not intentionally collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 can participate in all activities on the Site that do not require submission of personal information. They may view, but may not under any circumstances participate in activities that require submission of personal information, such as message boards, contests or sweepstakes. 

In addition we take particular care when processing the personal information of children aged 13 or older to ensure that such information is processed in accordance with the Act. 

**How we use personal information**

We may use personal information collected from the Site to enable your efficient use of the services on the Site, as well as for marketing, promotions, research, analysis, product service and development. We may occasionally use your personal information to contact you by telephone, fax, email, SMS or otherwise in writing to inform you about our products. 

We will not use your personal information for marketing or promotional purposes without having first obtained your consent to do so. In any further marketing or promotional communications we send to you, we will give you the opportunity to withdraw your consent to receiving such communications in the future. 

We may also use your personal information for the purposes of: 

processing and administering your registration as a member and/or use of paid-for services; 

performing any contracts concluded between you and us (including our _Terms of Use_ ); 

running competitions and other promotional events; 

conducting surveys as to quality of services via the Site; 

miscellaneous customer service correspondence (such as notifying you of changes to our services); 

processing details of your personal interests and preferences submitted to us via the Site; and 

processing details of your visits to the Site (including traffic data, location data and other communication data) and your online activity on the Site (including information on your game usage, such as your scores and rankings). 

We reserve the right to monitor your account and records to check any complaint or allegation of abuse, infringement of third-party rights or any other unauthorised use of the Site. 

**Disclosure of your personal information**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006 (whether based within or outside the European Economic Area). 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties where: 

they provide products or services to us in connection with your use of the Site; 

we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 

our company or substantially all of our assets are to be acquired by a third party, in which case we may disclose your personal information the prospective acquirer and personal data held by us about users of the Site will be one of the transferred assets; and/or 

we reasonably believe that we need to disclose your personal information to other person(s) (a) by order of any court or governmental or regulatory body of competent authority, (b) to comply with any legal obligation, (c) to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other contracts and/or (d) to protect our, our customers’ or any other third parties’ rights, property or safety (including exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction). 

We may also process your personal information to anonymise and aggregate it with other data and to disclose such anonymous and aggregate data to our affiliates and/or business partners. 

Except as required or allowed by law or as set out in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose or dispose of your personal information to any third party without your permission. 

**Tracking technology and IP addresses**

We may collect and process information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This comprises statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

We may, however, link IP addresses to personal data (such as a user’s country) and/or non-personal data (such as a user’s access location or usage record) in order to enforce our _Terms of Use_ or other user contracts, and we may block certain IP addresses from accessing all or any part of the Site in the event of a user abuse. In particular, our Japanese affiliate may use automated tracking tools to prevent or stop users from engaging in fraudulent activities or unauthorised uses of the Site (such as unauthorised commercial use of items obtained via game play). 

**Cookie technology**

A "cookie" is a small text file deposited on your computer's hard drive when you access a website. We may use cookies to monitor your use of the Site and to customise your experience of it. 

For further details, please refer to our _Cookies Policy_. 

**Where we store your personal information**

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers hosted by us or third parties providing hosting, payment or other services for us. 

The information we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "), including any destination where the privacy laws of the country concerned may be different and less protective than those of EEA countries. It may also be processed by personnel operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such personnel may be engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details (where applicable) and the provision of support services. 

By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. 

**Information security**

We take every reasonable precaution to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information and to ensure that it will be processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or you have chosen) an account password that enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. You acknowledge and accept that others may intercept the personal information you provide to us, and that any such transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

One easy and important way to protect your personal information is to keep your account password confidential and to close your browser when you are away from your computer. 

You can check and edit the personal information we hold about you at any time via the Site or by contacting us by email or post (details _below_ ). 

**Other websites**

The Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible and accept no liability for the privacy practices or content of such websites. 

**Opting out**

If, at any time, you wish us to stop using your personal information or to correct any factual inaccuracies, just contact us by email or post (details _below_ ). Be sure to state "opt-out" in the subject line, and to include your full name, registered user ID (if any) and email address in the message. 

**Access to your information**

If you would like a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, just contact us by email or post (details _below_ ). Be sure to state "Copy personal information" in the subject line, and to include your full name, registered user ID (if any) and email address in the message. If requested, we will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete information about you on our files. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions on this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal information, you can email us at _eu.privacypolicy@square-enix.com_ or write to us at Square Enix Limited, Wimbledon Bridge House, 1 Hartfield Road, London SW19 3RU marking any correspondence for the attention of the Legal and Business Affairs Department. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review, and we may at any time update or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the modified Privacy Policy on the Site. You are encouraged to check the terms of our Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Site. 

**Last modified: 23 July 2012**
